Hi,
I'm Tzuyu Chang.
In this project,
I work as a full stack developer,
primarily focusing on front end optimization and presentation.
On the front end,
I bootstrapped our react application using typescript,
vite and tailwind.
I integrated the google maps APIs to build our core interactive map.
Featuring real-time station markers and availability badges,
I also developed the detailed station panels for historical and predictive data.
Along with the complete user authentication and profile interfaces to ensure smooth data flow.
I wrote the front end logic to unwrap API responses and format them perfectly for our rechart.
On the backend,
I decide the real time station status end point using an efficient sql alchemy.
Subquery with func.max to avoid expensive full table scans.
I was responsible for authoring the overview requirements.
And testing section for our final project report.
I'm also the scrum master for the sprint 1 and sprint 4.
Thank you!